I just put thirty here at the chevas.
Bro doesn't even tickle.
Look this here is crazy bro things are getting really Cara,
right bro?
Let's go to the assembly with a giant gym,
it's on there,
the guy said,
see you go there next door,
bro,
there's a shop there,
then it might be good for you to sell,
see and I'll get there,
right?
crazy
you,
you walk around here a lot OR not,
I walk straight around.
I'm a truffle seller.
I stay there,
here, Cara.
He threw some flyers at my hand and he said he'd give me
100 mangoes if I deliver the flyers then I'm going to fall in,
man.
Opportunities you will encounter.
I came here to sell truffles and the Cara's are in need of people to publicize.
See,
that's it,
bro.
All right,
leave it here,
O new that will open.
How are you going to keep that shape with a kid to look after?
You can,
you're at the gym and the boys can be
there playing in the kids area without a place,
it's really weird,
okay?
When you train,
you're setting up a new gym.
There's even a sauna inside.
All right guys,
how are you doing?
It's brother?
To keep that physique from the municipal guard,
catch the bandits in the new gym town opening there for those who bother.
Looks like Cara who is an influencer,
who sellsiro in a toolbox,
I've been told that,
you believe oh people,
all good for you.
I'm selling some bracelets,
I'm selling bracelets to buy a cell phone for me,
how much is a bracelet?
It's five and the key chain is one.
I want two of those.
Hand strengthened my hand's work,
oh what time,
oh
thank you bro thank you so much brother.
If you have more opportunity for a pamphlet,
then let me know.
Tamo together,
even needing
good bro.
Did see old man?
Yesterday I went to sell truffle there at a barbershop.
It's on and there's Rolando 1 event there now and it's going,
it's full of people there,
bro,
I'm going to sell it,
Cara,
it looks like the event is in there,
dammit,
and I need to think of a way to be attractive.
You know how I'm going to sell truffles inside a barbershop at a guys event?
Man,
it can't be invasive,
you know?
Of course I came up with a plan,
right, bro?
We do everything before arriving at the places,
investing in a basket.
I think I put it in my hood and lost it,
I'll have to borrow about 1 basket.
Hand
and i Got a
Oh it's Alive
take the test there, bro.
The trustworthy pix of India guys is more in the
act than the fact that you just charge a direct price.
Guys are comfortable consuming there,
choosing truffles and man is giving a good shot.
I bought the new one.
Tomorrow is children's day
.